<resources>
    <string name="app_name">POC_ScreenImplementation</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="msg_generic_no_data">No Data to Display</string>
    <string name="dummy_movie_short_description">It is a strange comment to make about a film set inside a prison,
        but "The Shawshank Redemption" creates a warm hold on our feelings because it makes us a member of a family.
        Many movies offer us vicarious experiences and quick, superficial emotions. "Shawshank" slows down and looks.
        It uses the narrator's calm, observant voice to include us in the story of men who have formed a community behind bars.
        It is deeper than most films; about continuity in a lifetime, based on friendship and hope.</string>
    <string name="reviews"><u>Reviews</u></string>
    <string name="dummy_movie_long_description">From Andy\'s arrival on the prison bus to the film\'s end, we see only how others see him - Red,
        who becomes his best friend, Brooks the old librarian, the corrupt Warden Norton, guards and prisoners. Red is our surrogate.
        He\'s the one we identify with, and the redemption, when it comes, is Red\'s.
        We\'ve been shown by Andy\'s example that you have to keep true to yourself, not lose hope,
        bide your time, set a quiet example and look for your chance.
        I guess it comes down to a simple choice, really," he tells Red. Get busy livin' or get busy dyin'.
        The key to the film\'s structure, I think, is that it\'s not about its hero,
        but about our relationship with him - our curiosity, our pity, our admiration. If Andy had been the heroic center,
        bravely enduring, the film would have been conventional, and less mysterious. But we wonder about this guy.
        Did he really kill those two people? Why does he keep so much to himself?
        Why can he amble through the prison yard like a free man on a stroll, when everyone else plods or sidles?
        People like excitement at the movies, and titles that provide it do well.
        Films about "redemption" are approached with great wariness; a lot of people are not thrilled by the prospect of a great film -
        it sounds like work. But there's a hunger for messages of hope, and when a film offers one,
        it's likely to have staying power even if it doesn't grab an immediate audience.</string>
</resources>
